Today we'll use the content from the expert DK
the One-Day Reset Method and this piece of content
surpass 90% of people in 6 months
Let me show you
How is such a flowchart created?
Of course, if you want to do it
You can also follow along with me step by step.
I think the most crucial thing is to learn how to use AI for creating graphics
and some fundamental methods for content creation
I come from a purely liberal arts background
and had never done anything related to art before
design and such
but I think this picture is quite well done
And the data in the chart I created is actually pretty good.
I can share with everyone
We have two cases
One is about surpassing 90% of people in six months.
The other one is the one-day reset method
This is my first time using the 'One-Day Reset Method'. Let me show you the 'One-Day Reset Method' first.
Because this is the first time I've used this multi-text mode
with AI
I just want to see if it can understand what I'm saying.
Okay, let me show you
On the right, this part you see is my prompt
I said, based on the content of DK's one-day reboot method
Create an infographic for me
Keep the characters unchanged
only
Actually, it's me
Here I go, haha you believe me? Here, let me show you
What you are seeing now is this content
The key content is divided into three stages
Write down the anti-patterns in the morning
write down the minimum credibility
What am I avoiding during the day
What was I doing at night
This is his day
How to change your life, an important content
Here is the annual goal
a one-month project
daily and game rules
Actually, this is the content of his long podcast that we saw
the core issues presented
Now with AI
We directly feed its content to the AI
Hey, can you tell me
What is DK's recent content all about?
This is the content that the AI deduced and fed back to me.
Okay, I'll send all this content—it's not called prompts
This is called key content
I sent it to him
It actually understands
It's about current AI-generated graphics
It's not that you think, if such a diagram
I need to tell him about the One-Day Reset Method
Just think about how complicated it is
First, I definitely need to visualize in my mind
What does this diagram look like
what it looks like on the top
left, right, bottom, and various color combinations
How should this character appear, right?
This is extremely complicated for me.
For us design novices
I think this thing is very complicated
So I just sent it to him directly like this
But unexpectedly, the outcome turned out to be quite good.
You can see, this is the feedback it gave me
is to create a 3:4 infographic for me
based on the content of DK's one-fill technique
Keep the character IP I provided unchanged
Of course, the character IP here
It's my own character IP.
Alright, keep going and take a look below
This is the content it generated for me. Isn't it great?
And the speed is incredibly fast.
at an extremely fast speed
generated different templates in various colors for me
So let me show you
another flowchart I gave it
It goes like this
You can take a look at the right side of Me
This part, the content it generated for me
How to surpass 90% of people in 6 months
Didn't I just explain to him what that content was about?
It's about the content of reshaping your life in one day.
But I don't want to tell him now
What is this core content about
I directly say how to surpass 90% of people in six months
surpass 90% of people
The content within these quotation marks is what I communicated to the AI.
Now that AI integrates both text
combined with an image-based model like this
Of course, it can also generate videos
so I felt that
I gave DK, such an important freelancer,
a super individual
when such an important piece of content was sent to him
He should also know, right?
As expected
He actually knew it
Well, he told me
Understand the character's image and style
He generated a DK-style design for me
Keep the character unchanged
Surpass 90% of people in 6 months, in addition to this content
The same text is completely error-free
and it's incredibly fast
Right, okay
So when it has already provided me with this content
Actually, what I want are the four visions of 1234
Can you explain it to me more clearly, right?
So I asked it to break it down for me
four different aspects numbered one to four
How should it be done
For example, let's look at the first one
Establish clear and positive goals
with reverse leap and ideal vision
This diagram is essentially zoomed in
added this part of the content
Doesn't it look very complete overall?
very complete
Then let's take a look at the reverse engineering of the goal
is in the second direction
Then he deconstructed this content
has also become more detailed and clear
So, if everyone wants to do that kind of more complex
When you hear important content in someone else's podcast
You think this content is very important
but are afraid of forgetting
we can use such AI-generated images to represent it, which we call an infographic
I think it's quite convenient.
I hope today's content is helpful to you.
If you find it helpful, remember to leave a comment in my comment section.
So if you'd like to see more content
you are also welcome to share more with me